[{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":15851,"timeElapsed":73399},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10150,"timeElapsed":83550},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":8420,"timeElapsed":91972},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3322,"timeElapsed":95295},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3481,"timeElapsed":98777},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4732,"timeElapsed":103511},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6097,"timeElapsed":109610},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4330,"timeElapsed":113941},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2607,"timeElapsed":116549},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980898928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":6322,"timeElapsed":124071},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":127029},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980904733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":129876},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980907955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3220,"timeElapsed":133098},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":135944},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":139064},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980917283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":142426},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980919745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2460,"timeElapsed":144888},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980924267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4521,"timeElapsed":149410},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980935500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10036,"timeElapsed":160643},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1649,"timeElapsed":162293},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980939092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":164235},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1699,"timeElapsed":165935},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950878,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10085,"timeElapsed":176021},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980954686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":179829},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4657,"timeElapsed":184487},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2923,"timeElapsed":187411},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980964497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2229,"timeElapsed":189640},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980966457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1958,"timeElapsed":191600},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":8954,"timeElapsed":201758},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1751,"timeElapsed":203510},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1785,"timeElapsed":205295},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3371,"timeElapsed":208668},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":210866},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3493,"timeElapsed":214360},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980992678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3460,"timeElapsed":217821},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1667,"timeElapsed":219489},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":221571},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":7581,"timeElapsed":230271},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981006780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1651,"timeElapsed":231923},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981009182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2400,"timeElapsed":234324},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981011322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2139,"timeElapsed":236465},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017082,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5759,"timeElapsed":242225},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5514,"timeElapsed":247740},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":249942},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981027802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":252945},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981030099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2297,"timeElapsed":255242},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981032297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2196,"timeElapsed":257440},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981040213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6805,"timeElapsed":265356},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981041761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1546,"timeElapsed":266904},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981044849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":269992},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981047154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":272297},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981049073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1917,"timeElapsed":274216},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981050711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1637,"timeElapsed":275854},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981053608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2896,"timeElapsed":278751},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981056321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2711,"timeElapsed":281464},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981059991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3668,"timeElapsed":285133},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":8428,"timeElapsed":294510},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981070947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1579,"timeElapsed":296090},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981072849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1901,"timeElapsed":297992},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981074438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1588,"timeElapsed":299581},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2074,"timeElapsed":301656},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1631,"timeElapsed":303289},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":306003},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981083011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2150,"timeElapsed":308154},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981085859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2847,"timeElapsed":311002},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7763,"timeElapsed":319845},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":321794},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981098437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1785,"timeElapsed":323580},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981100465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":325608},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3355,"timeElapsed":328964},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981108127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4305,"timeElapsed":333270},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981111302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":336445},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981113330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":338473},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981118200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4869,"timeElapsed":343343},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981124352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4931,"timeElapsed":349495},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981126098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1745,"timeElapsed":351241},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981128088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1989,"timeElapsed":353231},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981130760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":355903},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981132750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1989,"timeElapsed":357893},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981134962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":360105},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981140206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5243,"timeElapsed":365349},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981143164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":368307},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981145592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2426,"timeElapsed":370734},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981150027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":375170},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981153025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2997,"timeElapsed":378168},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981155253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2227,"timeElapsed":380396},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981157435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":382578},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":384894},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981161917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2165,"timeElapsed":387060},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981164210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":389353},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981167909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3697,"timeElapsed":393052},{"subjectID":"oj1g3msuxm","prolificID":"6023f94d1951e70ae21770ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b49d0983520328206f6a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981171378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3468,"timeElapsed":396521}]